<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wireguard on Ranvier Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ranvier.net/tags/wireguard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in wireguard on Ranvier Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 20:03:30 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ranvier.net/tags/wireguard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireguard AppIndicator</title>
      <link>https://blog.ranvier.net/2019/12/wireguard-appindicator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 20:03:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ranvier.net/2019/12/wireguard-appindicator/</guid>
      <description>Wireguard AppIndicator At the time of writing, December of 2019, there exists no simple to use graphical interface for managing Wireguard connections as far as I&amp;rsquo;m concerned. To resolve this issue, I wanted to make an AppIndicator with the following capabilities:
 View status of Wireguard interface Enable and disable Wireguard interface View and copy the IP address of the interface  I also wanted to be able to use this on both Gnome Shell systems and systems with only support for AppIndicators, so the script is able to be used as either a standalone script running in the background or as a Gnome Shell extension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireguard Management System - Concept Introduction</title>
      <link>https://blog.ranvier.net/2019/12/wireguard-management-system-concept-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 23:49:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ranvier.net/2019/12/wireguard-management-system-concept-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Wireguard is a beautiful thing 😭. But one thing that I have found to be a point of contention is the lack of a simple interface for managing an existing Wireguard server. From some light browsing, I have found a couple of solutions that are mainly geared towards enterprise use or paid services but no simple FOSS CLI alternatives. Therefore, I feel that it would be nice to have a simple Bash script or Python script to accomplish this task.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>